Yes, sir. I redrafted the contracts
to include the new stipulations.
-Then where are they?
-I'm faxing the revisions now.
Did you make all the changes I asked for?
Yes. I included the four percent increase
and the extra 2 million.
No, no. If it's a four percent increase then
you have to add at least 3 million dollars.
That's not what I was told.
-Who told you that?
-Their lawyers.
They're all idiots! I don't understand
this total lack of communication.
It's okay. I just had no way of knowing, sir.
Look, this is what I need you to do.
-Sir, could I put you on hold for a second?
-Okay.
-Thanks. Hi, Jody.
-Mr. Harper wants to see you in his office.
-Great. Of course.
-Still want me to fax those?
You don't have to. I'm not even done yet.
You should go home.
-Are you sure?
-It's late.
I don't want your parents to worry.
Get out of here.
-Okay. Merry Christmas, Angela.
-Merry Christmas, Jody.
Hi, Lorraine. Of course I'm going to make it.
Just let me call you back. Okay?
In a few minutes, I promise. Okay.
Still on the Morgan deal?
What can I do for you, Jim?
I...
I don't know how to...
Angela, I feel terrible about what happened.
It's fine. Let's just not worry about it, okay?
No, it's not okay. I acted like a real jerk.
I had too many drinks and... You know
how these Christmas parties can be.
We had a baby last year, and...
It's been a hard year.
I'm sure that it has.
I simply want to tell you
that I'm really, really sorry. Okay?
Apology accepted.
Thanks. Merry Christmas, Angela.
You too, Jim.
You calling me from work?
Thought you were going home first.
-I brought everything with me. Don't worry.
Get over here, Angie.
God, I am
so late with this dinner.
Did you pick up the Santa Claus costume?
I hope you didn't forget it.
It's in the car.
I think Dad is more excited than the kids.
I can't wait to get out of here
and see you guys.
Jimmy, put that back.
We're having dinner soon.
-You want Santa to come tonight or not?
Mommy, I want Santa to come.
Then help me set the table.
-Please don't be late.
-I won't. I promise.
-Okay, bye.
-Bye.
Okay.
-Oh, Jesus!
-My God!
-Sorry, Angela...
-It's okay.
I was just locking up the floors.
I didn't know anybody would be working
this late on Christmas Eve.
-Me neither.
-Sorry.
I'll come back later, all right?
Actually, if you wouldn't
mind waiting, I'll lock my office
-and take the elevator down with you.
-Sure.
Two seconds.
Do you work all night?
Yeah, but they're closing the building
for the next three days.
-Besides, I get New Year's Eve off.
-That's good.
I hope to get home in time
for the girls to open up the presents.
-How are they?
-Great.
-Your parents can't stand me.
-You're wrong. They love you.
-So, where are you going this evening?
-I'm going to my sister's house in Jersey.
I thought of you more as
an Upper East Side girl.
Upper east side of Maine, actually.
I grew up on a farm.
Now, I'm having trouble believing that.
Hey, don't let the fancy clothes fool you.
I keep it real.
Is that what you call it? Keeping it real?
-Goodnight, Karl.
-Merry Christmas, Angela.
You too. I'll see you soon.
I promise you I'm leaving right now.
I know. I'm sorry, but I'm in the elevator.
Twenty-five minutes, tops.
I can't hear you. What?
Lorraine, you're breaking up.
Hello?
You have got to be kidding.
Come on.
Oh, God. What am I gonna do?
I'm getting out of the car
is what I'm gonna do.
Oh, shit.
Hello?
Jesus!
Rocky, what are you doing? Heel.
Stay. Down.
-Sorry about that.
-It's okay.
Look, can you unlock the door
to the elevator room?
My car won't start, and I need to
get upstairs and get a cab.
Yeah, I can.
I've just got to find my key cards.
Sorry. Where are those darn keys?
I'm about to do my rounds anyway, so...
-Okay, great.
-What happened to your car?
-I have no idea.
-You probably left the lights on.
I don't think so. I'm usually pretty good
about that kind of thing.
People do it all the time. It's instinctive.
You drive down here, it's dark... It happens.
Here we go.
-Great.
-You know, actually...
I have a charger in the back, so if it is
your battery probably you could use that.
Thank you, but... I really should
just take a cab. I'm so late as it is.
No, no. It would probably take longer
to get a cab. It's Christmas Eve.
So... I don't know. Up to you.
Whatever you want.
-How long will it take?
-Just a few minutes.
Now with beautiful Metropolitan
Opera House in the background,
let's check out
the temperatures in the Tri-State Area.
-Which way to your car?
-Over there.
Okay.
Working late, huh? I know how you feel.
These are pretty reliable cars
for the most part, right?
They're supposed to be.
All right. Positive...
Negative.
-All right, try it. Turn her over.
-Okay.
Strange.
Hang on. Can you turn your headlights on?
Weird. Try turning the keys again.
-Damn it.
-All right. I guess turn the headlights off.
You know what?
That's it.
You've been a great help, but I give up.
Sorry. I don't know what happened.
I thought I could do something.
You've been great. Could you just
let me in the elevator room now?
I was just trying to help.
I know. And I appreciate it. Thank you.
Hey, I know you're upset
about your car not starting, but...
It's the holidays. It's time to be thankful.
You know what? You're right.
-Yeah?
-I should be thankful.
I, uh...
I prepared
a small Christmas meal for myself.
You could join me if you want.
-I'm just kidding.
-Oh, sorry. I'm exhausted.
But thanks for your help.
You're welcome. Maybe some other time?
Sure.
All right.
Here you go. You sure
you don't want me to call you a cab?
-No. I've got a number in my bag.
-Suit yourself. Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
Karl?
Hi. Can I get a car
at 2370 Park Avenue, please?
Are you sure? No, that's okay.
I'll wait. Thanks.
Lorraine, you won't believe what happened.
No, my car wouldn't start.
Just start without me, and I'll be there
within the hour and I'll make it up to them.
Okay. I'll see you soon. Bye.
Hello? Oh, great. Thank you!
Okay. Okay.
Oh, come on.
What?
This is not happening. Is this a joke?
God, no, you gotta be kidding me.
Karl? Where are you? Is anybody here?
Come on, come on, come on.
What?
One second, okay? I'll be right back.
Just one second.
Hello, can you hear me?
I've got a cab waiting for me.
Can you open the front gate, please?
Hello?
No... Wait!
No! Damn it!
Why would you leave me here?
Wake up! The cab just left.
Hey! I'm still in here! Wait!
Great.
It's okay.
Hello?
Stop being paranoid.
Go down to the office.
Hello?
Oh, fuck!
Ho, ho, ho! Merry Christmas!
You've been a good little girl.
Wait. It's okay. You're all right. Okay?
All right?
You're not looking so good. Are you okay?
Take it easy. It's okay.
-What happened to me? What time is it?
-You just fell. You'll be all right.
I don't feel good. I'm going to be sick.
I'll get you some water.
Be careful! You're gonna hurt yourself.
Try to stay calm.
Okay.
It's okay. Here. Okay?
I'm going to help you up, okay?
Here we go.
There you go. It's okay.
All right. Try to relax while I clean this up.
Okay.
Clean this up. Okay.
All right. I'll be right back.
Hungry? I've got turkey,
mashed potatoes, cranberries,
and I've even got some cornbread.
Oh, man. I'm sorry about this.
I was just teasing.
I didn't mean to scare you.
I hope it's still warm.
If not, I have a microwave.
Are you feeling any better?
What happened to my clothes?
Like I said, you fell
and your clothes got dirty...
Maybe you'd like some wine.
Help you relax a little bit, you know?
I don't know what you're doing,
but you'd better just fucking untie me.
This is a California wine.
It's Sonoma County. That's where I'm from.
It's beautiful up there.
Where are you from?
-What do you want?
-I want to know where you're from.
I'm from Readfield.
-Readfield. Where's that?
-Please, tell me what you want.
I just want to know where Readfield is.
And I want you to relax.
Cheers.
I'll make a toast.
Here's to good friends and hometowns
and Readfield. Wherever that is.
-Listen...
-Tom.
Tom.
I have someplace to be. I have obligations.
Yeah. I know. Way too many.
You need time for yourself. You don't need
to be at everyone's beck and call.
Then maybe we should
get a drink in the new year.
I've already prepared everything.
It's all here.
I know, and it looks really good.
Yeah? Great. Well, let's eat.
I'm starving.
Tom, this is really sweet of you,
and I mean that.
But my whole family is expecting me.
I have plans.
I guess some plans are made to be broken.
Do you want to say grace or should I?
Hell, let's skip it.
I've never been religious anyway.
Bon appétit.
What do you like to do?
After work and stuff? I guess, hobbies.
That's a mundane question,
but I guess people ask that
just to get to know each other, right?
I read. Right now I'm reading Hemingway,
The Sun Also Rises.
And you really should eat.
It's gonna get cold.
Anyway, in the book
this guy loves this girl so much
that he's willing to forgive
everything that she does.
Even her infidelities.
That's a pretty intense story, but...
That's what love is supposed to be, right?
My boyfriend is gonna get worried
and come looking for me, Tom.
If I don't show up,
he'll come looking for me.
He knows where I work.
How long have you guys been
dating or hanging out?
-Two years.
-Two years?
-Do you live together?
-That's none of your fucking business.
That's not very nice dinner talk.
Yeah, we live together, okay?
Two years...
That's more than a boyfriend.
That sounds like wedding bells.
Do you have any plans?
-Yes.
-What does your fiancé do?
He's a journalist.
I knew he had to be smart.
What kind of journalist?
-Sports.
-What paper?
-Post.
-I read The Post.
-What's his name?
-Mark Clayton.
Clayton. I don't remember that name.
-I have one over here.
-It's The Post online.
It's amazing
that you're able to keep a relationship
with the amount of hours you work.
He must get really lonely
when you have to work late, right?
Do you love him?
Does he love you?
I'm only asking because I'm worried about
how quickly he's going to get here.
I'm sure he's already on his way.
Right. He's probably
on the Harlem River Drive as we speak.
-What kind of car does he drive?
-I don't know.
You don't know what kind of car
your fiancé drives?
-Toyota, I think.
-Toyota. That is a fast car.
He can be here a lot sooner
than I was thinking.
He could be coming down
this ramp right now.
You haven't been very talkative
since we met.
But now you're telling me all about
your boyfriend. Oh, sorry, your fiancé.
So either we've become best friends
over dinner or you're lying to me.
I'm guessing
you're lying to me.
You don't really have a boyfriend, do you?
But you want one.
You want somebody who cares about you...
-Worries about you...
-Please, don't.
You've got a great family.
You've got Lorraine.
Jimmy and Rose. They love you.
They're probably getting worried about you.
Maybe we should give them a call. Yeah?
Tell them you're okay.
What do you think?
What should we say?
I know.
We should say you made other plans.
No. You probably already said that one.
You know what?
You should think of something.
You're a good liar.
Go ahead.
Go!
No.
Hello? Hello?
Hey, Rosie.
Can you get your mommy on the phone?
Who's calling, please?
-It's Auntie Angie.
-Mommy, it's Aunt Angie.
Give me a second, okay?
Hey, where are you?
-Angela?
-I'm not feeling well.
What do you mean?
We're all waiting for you.
She says she's not feeling well.
That's what she said the last time.
Can I talk to my sister, please?
Where are you, Angie?
She's got a real job. It's not like...
Angela?
I went home.
What's wrong? Where is she?
I don't understand.
Last time I talked to you,
you were on your way.
What about the costume?
Let's just eat.
You should know your sister by now.
It would be nice if you'd try
and put your family
ahead of your work sometimes.
That's enough. Give me the phone.
Angie, what's wrong?
Hello? I can't hear her.
Sweetie? Can you hear me?
-Hi, Mom. I'm here.
-Honey, what happened? Where are you?
I don't know.
I think it's the flu.
You really sound terrible.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah. I just need some rest.
Okay.
Rest up and hopefully you'll
feel better for lunch tomorrow.
And don't worry about the costume, okay?
-Merry Christmas, angel. I love you.
-I love you too, Mom.
That was the best Christmas present
anyone's ever given me.
Thank you.
And now I have a present for you.
Go ahead.
Open it.
Aren't you even curious?
Yes.
Bet you're curious now.
Okay. Enough torture.
Watch. It's all cued up.
-Why are you showing this to me?
-Wait.
You fucked up now, asshole.
Sorry you had to see that.
You want to go for a stroll?
These guys always do whatever they want.
Here we go.
Rocky, sit down!
Why did you do that?
Rocky, shut the fuck up!
-Let me help you up.
-Don't.
-Don't touch me!
-I'm not gonna hurt you. All right?
You're hurting my arm.
That's because you won't
relax your arms. Okay?
-Come on.
-Just let me go. I won't tell anyone.
Yeah, I believe you.
I just need to show you something.
Let's put that all behind us, yeah?
Here we go.
Uh-oh.
I think I drank too much wine.
I really shouldn't be driving.
I'm just kidding.
You know, I've seen you drive
out of here so many times.
Strange being in the car with you.
It's great, actually.
-I thought you said we were taking a drive.
-We are.
Then why are we going down, Tom?
It's freezing out there.
Besides, this is gonna be much better.
Why are we down here, Thomas?
Tom?
Oh, my God, Tom.
What is this?
This is my present to you.
I want you to take this and show him.
Show him what?
Show him you're not a slut.
Take this and teach him he can't be
touching every woman he wants.
Are you talking about
what happened in the elevator?
Oh, Tom, no. You don't understand.
That was a mistake.
A stupid mistake.
-What? He tried to rape you.
-No.
He got a little out of hand at a party, Tom.
He hardly tried to rape me.
Look, he was drunk. He apologized.
Oh, he apologized.
You think you're the first woman
he tried to do this to?
I've seen him try to touch
every woman in the building.
-He's a pervert. A degenerate.
-No.
He's a good man, Tom.
Look at him. He has a family.
He has a wife. Tom, please don't.
Tom, Tom...
Stop calling out my name, all right?
I know what you're trying to do.
You're trying to humanize yourself,
like you're some poor victim.
I told you, I'm not gonna hurt you!
All right?
Stop calling out my name!
Enough's enough!
Tom, Tom, Tom!
How many times can you say it?
Okay.
I know you're a person, okay?
I'm a person, too.
I know you have feelings.
I have feelings, too.
I care about your feelings.
He's the one you should be scared of.
He's the one who has no feelings.
So if you want to help him,
take this and teach him a lesson.
I told you, he apologized.
What? He can just apologize
and then he can do it again?
And then he's just gonna
apologize again and then...
You've got to stop letting these assholes
have their way with you!
Tom, please believe me.
It was just a misunderstanding, Tom.
Tom, Tom!
Just stop calling out my name! I told you!
-Didn't I?
-Yes! Yes.
-I'm sorry, but you're scaring me.
-Jesus! When are you gonna understand?
I'm here to help you.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Okay.
I'll do it.
You untie me and I'll do it.
No. Oh, no. Whoa.
You're a good person.
You're a good person, too.
I should have never asked
you to do this. I'm sorry.
No. It's okay because I want to.
You just have to untie me
and I'll do it for you.
No, no. It's my job to protect you.
No, Tom, listen to me. It's not.
Please don't do anything.
Don't try to run away, okay?
Can I trust you?
-Can I trust you?
-Yes.
You can trust me.
I'm sorry. Oh God, I'm sorry.
So...
You like to touch girls, do you?
No? Look at her.
I said look at her.
Does she look happy to you? Huh?
Yeah.
You messed with the wrong girl.
What makes you think
you deserve her? Huh?
What gives you the right?
You're something else, you know that?
You pretentious Ivy League piece of shit.
You don't own the world and everyone in it.
What is a guy like you thinking
when he puts his hands all over a girl
who obviously is not interested?
Who is obviously not a slut?
Because that's what
you think they are, right?
Yeah? I can't hear you. What did you say?
What? Can you speak up?
Because you can't talk your way
out of this one, can you?
-Why am I even wasting my time with you?
No!
-What? Angela, he deserves it!
-Don't do anything, Thomas, please!
No!
Stop it! Stop it!
Way to ruin Christmas, asshole.
Well, he won't be bothering you again.
Where are we going?
We can't just leave him here.
You have to get him.
What? Why are you defending him?
I'm not. I'm not.
Do you like this?
Do you like to get touched?
You like it when he touches you
in the parking garage?
-Do you want to get laid here?
-You know that's not true.
So what is it? A career thing?
Did you fuck him to get a promotion?
We can't leave him here.
You're right. I'm sorry.
We shouldn't leave him here.
Wait! Thomas, stop!
-What are you doing?
-We're gonna just take him for a little drive.
What are you doing?
Tom, stop the car! Please!
Please stop! Please!
Stop it! What are you doing, Tom? No!
No! No!
Oh, my God!
No, please! Oh, my God! Don't do this.
Please don't! No!
Thomas, no.
You're a good person, Thomas.
Please don't do this.
No! God, no! Stop it!
Hey! Hey!
Where are you going?
Angela! Come back!
You fucked him, didn't you? Liar!
Hey! Down here!
Can you hear me? Help!
Down here! Can't you hear me?
Good boy.
Sit. Good boy.
Stay right there, Rocky.
Stay there.
Help me! Help me, please!
Help me, please!
Someone's trying to kill me! Help me!
Help me!
Somebody's trying to kill me!
Oh, Karl. Where are you?
Oh, my God.
Angela?
Please.
If anyone can hear me...
I'm trapped in the underground parking
structure of the Arcadia Building.
It's 2370 Park Avenue.
Someone's trying to kill me.
Angela.
Angela, come out.
Shit.
Angela?
Can we talk about this?
Looks like somebody's
playing games, huh, Rocky?
Angela?
Come on.
Come on. Lobby.
Come on. Lobby. Come on.
Why is it fucking locked?
Angela!
Hello?
Hello? Can anyone hear me?
Please, hello?
Answer, please?
Yes?
Five Brothers Security here. Hello?
Yes. I'm here. Can you hear me?
I can hear you fine. How can I help you?
I'm being kidnapped.
I work at Brieter, Smith and Steinberg.
It's 2370 Park Avenue
and I'm hiding in the elevator.
Please can you call 911?
Calm down, miss.
Is there someone with you right now?
No, he's outside in the parking lot.
He already killed someone else.
Did you see him do it?
Yes! His name is Thomas and he's
the parking attendant in my building.
If you'll just please hurry. I'm in danger.
Ma'am, you have got to relax
and take a deep breath.
How do you fucking expect me to relax?
This man is trying to kill me!
Can you please try to understand
and call the cops?
Please just call 911!
The police?
No. I'm sure he's just trying to help you.
Right?
Angela?
Are you still there?
Listen you fuck-face, I called the cops
and I'm gonna stay down here
as long as it takes until they get here,
so I suggest that you get the fuck out!
I just wanna talk to you.
That's why I pretended to be
someone else, okay? So don't be upset.
Will you come out? I was just kidding.
Just go to hell!
Don't you understand? I did it for you.
That guy showed you no respect.
Why won't you talk to me, Angela?
Just give me a chance.
If you just give us a chance,
it can work out.
You'll grow to like me.
That's usually what happens
when two people
are forced to be together
in a stressful situation.
They have to depend on one another.
And eventually they support each other.
They like each other.
Sometimes they even fall in love.
Angela.
Please don't do this.
Why won't you talk to me?
You know, I wish you had just
a little bit more respect for yourself.
I'm not coming out! Do you hear me?
I'm not fucking moving, you fuck!
Karl! Oh, no, please.
Karl!
Come on, Karl!
Angela?
You must be freezing out here.
Angela.
What a mess.
I think Karl is hurt.
Angela? Should we call him an ambulance?
That way he can go back to his kids
and family, and you can go to your sister's.
And I could stay here! In this parking lot!
All by myself!
Because that's obviously
what everybody wants!
Angela?
I just can't keep
chasing you around all night.
Besides, the whole place is locked.
Angela?
Where are you gonna go if you get away?
It's freezing out there.
You can't go out.
Angela?
Angela!
Way to ruin Christmas, Karl.
I'll have a blue
Christmas without you
I'll be so blue
Just thinking about you
Decorations of red
On a green Christmas tree
Won't be the same, dear
If you're not here with me
And when those blue
Snowflakes start falling
That's when those blue
Memories start calling
You'll be doing all right
With your Christmas of white
But I'll have a blue
Blue, blue, blue Christmas
You'll be doing all right
With your Christmas of white
But I'll have a blue
Blue, blue, blue Christmas
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Oh, yeah.
Do you want makeup?
Okay.
You have the most beautiful lips
I have ever seen in my life.
You're beautiful.
Thank you for accepting my invitation.
You have a wonderful body.
It was meant to be, babe.
Me and you.
Your skin...
It's soft.
Honey.
I love you. Angela, you know that, right?
Hello?
Shit.
I'm down here. Hello? Can you hear me?
It's okay.
Hello, Officer. Can I help you?
Can you open up the gate, please?
Yes, sir. I'll be right up.
I'm sorry. I have to do this.
Hey.
Sorry about that.
I was on the bottom floor doing my rounds.
What's going on tonight?
We got a call about a disturbance
at this address. Know anything about that?
No, it's been real quiet all night.
See anything, hear anything suspicious?
Like I said, I was just doing my rounds.
It's been really quiet.
I haven't seen anybody down here.
Any cars in there?
Well, it is a parking garage.
There's a few cars scattered
over here in this level.
On the second level there's a rental thing.
Like I said, there's been no one
around tonight. Except me and Rocky.
Two of you working here tonight.
Kind of. He's my dog.
He's down in the office right now.
We're gonna take a look around.
Get in the back. We'll give you a ride.
That's a great idea.
I've just gotta close this gate.
A lot of homeless people around here.
Thanks for the ride.
If you guys wanna
check out the other floors,
just keep going around this way.
But be careful on P3.
There's a broken water main, okay?
-We'll come back around.
-Okay.
What the hell's going on here, man?
Help me! Help!
Help me!
Sure you haven't seen
anything weird tonight?
No. Everybody left really early tonight.
You having a party in here?
No, no. It's just me and Rocky, not a party.
Got anybody coming over to visit?
You know, a little action?
Me? No. The company would fire me
if I had anyone down here tonight.
Especially at this hour.
Well, we don't want to break any rules.
Right, partner?
Not on my watch.
Come on, let's go.
Help me!
I've got to open the gate,
so I'll just take the stairs.
Let's do it.
Open.
Wait!
You guys stay warm.
-You keep your eyes and ears open, huh?
-You bet.
-Merry Christmas.
-You too, buddy.
Wait! Wait!
911.
-Yes, please, I need your help.
-All our lines are busy at the moment.
Please hold.
-Someone will be with you shortly.
-Hello?
Thank you.
All our lines are busy at the moment.
Please hold.
911. All our lines are busy at the moment.
Rock? Rocky!
Why would you do that?
He's just an animal.
Angela!
Why would you kill a defenseless animal?
After all I did for you? To help you?
This is what I get?
You killed my dog!
Answer. Please answer.
Angela?
You're really starting to piss me off!
Angela!
Hello? Are you there?
Hello? This is the police.
Is somebody there?
Is this an emergency?
If you can hear me, please say something.
Tap the phone, let me know
if you're there. Hello?
This is the police. This is 911.
Are you okay? Are you there? Hello?
You're trying to get me fired, aren't you?
Bet you'd really like that.
But, honey...
What are we gonna do then?
We couldn't just live off of your salary.
Angela!
Shit!
Let's fucking do this.
You want to fuck with me?
Come on!
Come on, you chicken shit!
Angela?
Let me help you out, okay?
Help me? You're gonna help me?
Why don't you let me help you,
for a change? Motherfucker!
What the fuck are you doing, Angela?
Come back here, now! Let me go!
Come over here
and get me out of this right now!
Why are you doing this, Angela?
Angela.
Angela? I just wanted us to be friends.
I'm alone.
I'm always alone.
Why can't we just
spend more time together?
Angela? Wait.
Why?
Why can't we be friends?
Why can't we just
spend Christmas together?
Do you hear me? You stupid, fucking cunt!
Angela, wait. I didn't...
Merry Christmas, Thomas.
No! No! No!
No! No!
You all right, lady?